https://willsieco.com/terms-conditions/

JUDICIAL & LEGAL ROBES
THE BASIC (GOOD)
THE CHANCERY (BETTER)
THE JURIST (BEST)
PULPIT ROBES
THE DIVINITY (BEST)
THE HERALD (GOOD)
THE WESLEY (BETTER)
Brands
M2000™LITTLE SCHOLAR™FREEDOM™FINEST QUALITY™ULTRA GREENWillsie Cap & Gown Co.®Graduate Choice™LUXURY CHAINETTE™
Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
FOR DISCOUNTS ON BULK ORDERS OVER 100 UNITS, PLEASE CALL US AT 1-800-370-0931 OR CLICK HERE FOR A FREE QUOTE.
For International Orders Or Order Inquiries, Call Us On 1-800-370-0931
JUDICIAL & LEGAL ROBES
THE BASIC (GOOD)
THE CHANCERY (BETTER)
THE JURIST (BEST)
PULPIT ROBES
THE DIVINITY (BEST)
THE HERALD (GOOD)
THE WESLEY (BETTER)
Terms & Conditions
The following Terms and Conditions apply to the use of this Web site as well as all transactions conducted through the site.
SHIPPING & DELIVERY
U.S. ORDERS
All items are shipped via FedEx.Orders placed less than 2 weeks before the ceremony date may require expedited shipping.
INTERNATIONAL ORDERS
For international orders, please call us to place your order at 1-800-370-0931, Monday to Friday between 8:30 AM to 4:30 PM (Central Standard Time).
SHIPPING DAYS
Shipping days do NOT include weekends or federal holidays.  Any orders placed outside of business hours will not be processed until the next business day.  Our business hours are from Monday to Friday between 8:30 AM to 4:30 PM (Central Standard Time).
RETURN POLICY
Items must be returned within 15 days of receipt.Returned items may be subject to a restocking fee.All items must be returned unused in the original containers.No returns on custom products unless defective.
Privacy Policy
Table of Contents
Introduction
Acceptance of Terms
What Information We Collect/Receive
The Information Collected/Received from Your School
The Information Collected/Received from our Sales Representatives and Through Paper Order Forms
The Information Collected by or Through Third-Party Companies
How to Opt Out of Third-Party Interest-Based Advertising
How the Information is Shared
Information we may Contribute to Cooperative Databases
Accessing and Modifying Information and Communication Preferences
How We Protect Your Information
Important Notices to Non-U.S. Residents
External Websites
Children
How Can You Manage Personal Information You Submit?
Changes to This Privacy Policy
How to Contact Us
CCPA Privacy Notice
Do Not Sell My Information
Introduction
Effective Date: January 1, 2020
We at American Achievement Corporation (“AAC,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) have created this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected when you visit any of our websites, which include, without limitation, http://www.balfour.com/, http://www.artcarved.com/, http://gradgowns.us/, http://www.delavoy.ca/, https://www.gaspard.ca/, https://www.buildagrad.ca/, https://buildagrad.com/, https://www.keepsakebowling.com/, http://www.balfoursports.com/, http://www.universityphoto.com/ , https://www.artneedle.com/, https://willsieco.com/, http://gradgowns.com/, http://mygraduationstore.com/, and http://www.gradimages.com, (“Websites”), access our mobile app, which may be accessible through mobile devices and tablets (the “Mobile App”), access and use our services provided through the Websites and the Mobile App (“Services”), or purchase our products (“Products”). The Websites and the Mobile App are collectively referred to as the “Online and Digital Properties.”
Acceptance of Terms
By visiting our Websites, accessing our Mobile App, accessing and using our Services, and/or purchasing our Products, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in the Terms of Use.
What Information We Collect/Receive
We collect and/or receive the following categories of information:
Contact Information
When you contact us through the “Contact Us” page, or sign up to receive special offers & promotions, or sign up to become a Registered User, you will be asked to provide certain information which may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, and student’s name if you are registering on behalf of a student (collectively, the “Contact Information”).
If you sign in using your Facebook or any other social media account, you are authorizing AAC to collect, store, and use, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, any and all information that you agreed that Facebook, Inc., or such other social media company could provide to AAC through its Application Programming Interface. Such information may include, without limitation, your first and last name, username, profile picture, unique social media identifier and access token, and e-mail address.
Billing Information
In order to submit orders through the Online and Digital Properties you will be required to provide certain information in addition to the Contact Information noted above. Such information may include PayPal, Payflow account information, debit card number, credit card number, billing address, and similar information (collectively, the “Billing Information). For orders submitted through the Online and Digital Properties, the Billing Information is collected, stored and processed by our third-party payment vendors.
You may also submit orders by using our paper order forms. If you submit orders using our paper order forms, you will be required to fill in the Billing Information on our paper forms. Once we receive your paper order forms, our customer service representatives will enter your Billing Information through our Websites in order to allow our third-party payment vendors to collect, store and process such information. All paper order forms are also scanned by our third-party service providers into encrypted files which are stored on our servers. The encrypted files do not contain the Billing Information. We also store your original paper order forms in locked cabinets until your order is processed. Once your order is processed, your original paper order forms are destroyed.
Order Information
If you wish to purchase our Products, you will also be required to provide us with certain additional information such as your name, shipping address, and the Products you wish to order (“Order Information”). If you place an order as a guest (without creating an account as a Registered User), we will use your Order Information solely as necessary to process your order.
Geolocational Information
Certain features and functionalities of the Online and Digital Properties are based on your location. In order to provide these features and functionalities while you are using a mobile device, we may, with your consent, automatically collect geolocational information from your mobile device or wireless carrier and/or certain third-party service providers. Such information is collectively called the “Geolocational Information.” Collection of Geolocational Information occurs only when the Mobile App is running on your mobile device. You may decline to allow us to collect such Geolocational Information, in which case we will not be able to provide certain features of the Mobile App to you.
Other Information
In addition to the Contact Information, Order Information, and Geolocational Information, we may collect and/or receive additional information (collectively, the “Other Information”). Such Other Information may include:
From your Activity. In an ongoing effort to improve our Online and Digital Properties, we automatically collect certain information when visitors visit the Websites and Registered Users use the Online and Digital Properties, such as your IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Websites visitors visit, similar information concerning your use of the Online and Digital Properties, information about a mobile device, including universally unique ID (“UUID”), App type and version (e.g., iOS or Android), carrier and country location, hardware and processor information (storage, chip speed, camera resolution, NFC enabled, and network type (WiFi, 2G, 3G, 4G, 5G). If you use the “Shop Your School” feature on the Online and Digital Properties, we will collect the zip code that you use to use this feature, together with your IP address and school information.
From Cookies. We may use both session cookies, which expire once you close your web browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your computer until you delete them and other technologies to help us collect data and to enhance your experience with the Online and Digital Properties. Cookies are small text files a website can use to recognize a repeat visitor to the website. We may use cookies for various purposes, including to authenticate users, personalize your experience, analyze which portions of the Online and Digital Properties are visited most frequently, and measure and optimize advertising and promotional effectiveness. If you do not want us to deploy cookies in your browser, you can opt out by setting your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still use the Online and Digital Properties, although your ability to use some of the features may be affected.
Third-Party Analytics. We also use third-party analytics services to evaluate your use of the Online and Digital Properties, compile reports on activity, collect demographic data, analyze performance metrics, and collect and evaluate other information relating to the Online and Digital Properties and Internet usage. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By accessing and using the Online and Digital Properties, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. For more information on these third parties, including how to opt out from certain data collection, please visit the sites below.
For Google Analytics, please visit https://www.google.com/analytics
For Magento, please visit
https://magento.com/legal/terms/privacy
For Crazy Egg, please visit https://www.crazyegg.com
The Information Collected/Received from Your School
We may receive certain information about you from your school. Such information may include your name, and the Products you would like to order (“School Provided Information”). The School Provided Information shall be provided by your school in accordance with all applicable laws, including but not limited to Family Education and Privacy Act (“FERPA”).
The Information Collected/Received from our Sales Representatives and Through Paper Order Forms
We may receive your Contact Information, Billing Information and Order Information if you place your order with our sales representatives and/or using our paper order forms.
The Information Collected by or Through Third-Party Companies
We may share Other Information about you with third parties, including but not limited to, advertising companies, and our brand partners, for ad distribution and ad optimization (defined as the tailoring, targeting (i.e., behavioral, contextual, and retargeting), analyzing, managing, reporting, and optimizing of ads). These third parties may use cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs), and/or other technologies to collect Other Information for such purposes. Pixel tags enable us and these third-party advertising companies to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits the site on which the pixel tag is located in order to learn which advertisement brings a user to a given site. In addition, we may receive Other Information from advertisers, brand partners, and/or their service providers such as advertising identifiers, IP addresses, and post-conversion data.
How to Opt Out of Third-Party Interest-Based Advertising
If you wish to opt out of third-party interest-based advertising, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org and http://www.aboutads.info/choices for details on how to do so.
How the Information is Shared
You authorize us to use your Contact Information, Order Information, Geolocational Information, School Provided Information and Other Information (collectively, the “Information”) to provide and improve our Online and Digital Properties, Services and Products, to fulfill your requests and purchases; to send order notifications and marketing communications, to provide personalized and more convenient onsite shopping experience, to solicit your feedback, to inform you about our products and services and those of our promotional partners. We will use your phone number to send you updates about your order and marketing notifications via SMS. If you would like to opt-out of receiving such SMS, please contact us at
privacy@balfour.com.
You also authorize us to use and/or share Information as described below.
We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include providing technical assistance, customer service, marketing assistance, billing, and administration of our promotional programs. These other companies will have access to the Information only as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law.
In an ongoing effort to better understand our users, the Online and Digital Properties, and our Products and Services, we may analyze your Information in anonymized and aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Online and Digital Properties and/or such Products and Services. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, business and promotional partners, and other third parties. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe the Online and Digital Properties and our products and services to current and prospective business partners and investors and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
We may share some or all of your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, affiliates or other companies under common control with us.
As we develop our businesses, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, the Information may be part of the transferred assets.
To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose the Information: (i) when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency; or (ii) whenever we believe that disclosing such Information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of AAC or others.
We may share your Contact Information and Order Information with your school to determine your eligibility to receive the Products you order.
We may share your Contact Information, Order Information and School Provided Information with our sales representatives. All of our sales representatives will only use the consumer’s information consistent with the purposes described in the policy.
We may also share your credit card information in an anonymized manner with our business partners to create profiles to help us better market to our users.
We may share your Contact Information with your school counselors who will use the information to message you about your order.
Information we may Contribute to Cooperative Databases
We may contribute your Information to cooperative databases which give third parties subscribing for such databases access to your Information for the purposes of confirming viability of e-mails and fraud protection. If you do not wish to have your Information contributed to cooperative databases, please send an e-mail to
privacy@balfour.com.
Accessing and Modifying Information and Communication Preferences
If you have provided us any Contact Information and/or Order Information, you may access, remove, review, and/or make changes to certain elements of the same by logging in to your account. In addition, you may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of any AAC marketing e-mail. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process such requests in a timely manner. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our subscription databases. You cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to the Online and Digital Properties.
How We Protect Your Information
We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases or the databases of the third parties with which we may share such Information, nor can we guarantee that the Information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. If you send us an email, we cannot guarantee the security of any information contained therein because we do not have control over the security of incoming emails.
Important Notices to Non-U.S. Residents
The Online and Digital Properties and its servers are operated in the United States and elsewhere. Please be aware that your Information may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your country of origin. If you are located outside the United States and choose to use the Online and Digital Properties, you do so at your own risk.
External Websites
The Online and Digital Properties may contain links to third-party websites. (“External Sites”) AAC has no control over the privacy practices or the content of these External Sites. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these External Sites. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any such External Sites.
Children
The Online and Digital Properties are not intended for children. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information on the Sites. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Sites. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, we will use reasonable efforts to refrain from further using such personal information or maintaining it in retrievable form. If you believe we might have information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@balfour.com.
Furthermore, if you are under eighteen (18) years of age, then you (or your parent or legal guardian) may at any time request that we remove content or information about you that is posted on the Online and Digital Properties. Please submit any such request (“Request for Removal of Minor Information”) to
privacy@balfour.com, with a subject line of “Removal of Minor Information”. For each Request for Removal of Minor Information, please state “Removal of Minor Information” in the e-mail or letter subject line, and clearly state the following in the body:
the nature of your request;
the identity of the content or information to be removed;
whether such content or information if found on the Sites;
the location on content or information on the Sites (e.g., providing the URL for the specific web page the content or information is found on);
that the request is related to the “Removal of Minor Information”;
your name, street address, city, state, zip code, and e-mail address; and
whether you prefer to receive a response to your request by mail or e-mail.
We are not responsible for failing to comply with any Request for Removal of Minor Information that is incomplete, incorrectly labeled, or incorrectly sent.
Please note that the aforementioned removal does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of such content or information posted on the Online and Digital Properties.
Also, please note that we are not required to erase or otherwise eliminate, or to enable erasure or elimination of, such content or information in certain circumstances, such as, for example, when an international, federal, state, or local law, rule, or regulation requires us to maintain the content or information; when the content or information is stored on or posted to the Online and Digital Properties by a third party other than you (including any content or information posted by you that was stored, republished, or reposted by the third party); when we anonymize the content or information, so that you cannot be individually identified; when you do not follow the aforementioned instructions for requesting the removal of the content or information; and when you have received compensation or other consideration for providing the content or information.
How Can You Manage Personal Information You Submit?
Managing Communications With You. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving such emails by following the "unsubscribe" directions on the e-mails.
Updating or Correcting personal information. If you would like to review, correct, update or remove personal information about you that you previously provided to us, you may do so by sending us an e-mail at privacy@balfour.com, by calling us at 1-800-BALFOUR (800-225-3687) or by writing to us:
American Achievement Corporation
Attn: Privacy Officer 1550 W Mockingbird Lane Dallas, Texas 75235
For your protection, we will only implement such requests with respect to the personal information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that we are not responsible for correcting, updating or deleting any information in the databases of third parties with whom we have already shared your personal information.
For Nevada Residents Only: Effective October 1, 2019, Nevada law gives consumers in Nevada the right to restrict certain businesses from selling certain personal information to third parties if those third parties will license or sell such personal information to additional third parties. To exercise this right, please send an email to privacy@balfour.com. Provide the requested information (e.g., your complete name, street address, city, state, zip code, and email address).
Your California Privacy Rights. If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit
https://www.balfour.com/HelpCenter/Legal/CCPA%20Privacy%20Notice
Changes to This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on the Online and Digital Properties. By accessing the Online and Digital Properties, accessing our Services, and/or ordering our Products after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please be aware that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, our use of the Information is governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect the Information. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.
How to Contact Us
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us in one of the following ways:
Email: privacy@balfour.com
Phone: 1-800-BALFOUR (800-225-3687)
Or write to us at:
American Achievement Corporation 1550 W Mockingbird Lane Dallas, Texas 75235
CCPA Privacy Notice
PRIVACY STATEMENT-CALIFORNIA
This PRIVACY NOTICE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS supplements the information contained in the American Achievement Corporation Privacy Policy, which is incorporated by reference herein. This supplemental Privacy Statement-California applies to the Online and Digital Properties, but solely as to visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California (“consumers” or “you”). We adopt this notice to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) and other California privacy laws. Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this notice.
Information We Collect
We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device (“personal information”). In particular, we have collected the following categories of personal information from consumers within the last twelve (12) months:
Category
Examples
Collected
A. Identifiers.
A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, Social Security number, driver's license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.
YES
B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)).
A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories.
YES
C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.
Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information).
NO
D. Commercial information.
Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
YES
E. Biometric information.
Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or exercise data.
NO
F. Internet or other similar network activity.
Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.
YES
G. Geolocation data.
Physical location or movements.
YES
H. Sensory data.
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.
NO
I. Professional or employment-related information.
Current or past job history or performance evaluations.
NO
J. Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)).
Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records.
NO
K. Inferences drawn from other personal information.
Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
NO
Personal information does not include:
Publicly available information from government records.
De-identified or aggregated consumer information.
Information excluded from the CCPA's scope, like:
health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data;
personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.
We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources:
Directly from our customers.
Directly and indirectly from activity on the Online and Digital Properties. For example, from submissions through portals on our Websites or website usage details collected automatically.
From third-parties that interact with us in connection with the services we perform.
Use of Personal Information
We may use or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:
To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, we may use personal information about you to respond to your requests, fulfill your purchase requests, send you publications or other information, and to answer your questions.
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
To provide you with email alerts, event registrations and other notices concerning our products or services, or events or news, that may be of interest to you.
To improve our Online and Digital Properties and present their contents to you.
For testing, research, analysis and product development.
For our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, enhancing the Online and Digital Properties, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional messaging.
As necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our clients or others.
To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.
To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred.
We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.
Sharing Personal Information
We may disclose your personal information to a third party for a business purpose. When we disclose personal information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information for a business purpose:
Category A: Identifiers. Category B: California Customer Records personal information categories. Category D: Commercial Information Category F: Internet or other similar network activity
Category G: Physical location or movements
We disclose your personal information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:
Our affiliates.
Service providers.
Third parties to whom you or your agents authorize us to disclose your personal information in connection with products or services we provide to you.
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have not sold any personal information.
Your Rights and Choices
The CCPA provides consumers (California residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.
Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights
You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.
The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.
The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).
If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing:
sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and
disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.
Deletion Request Rights
You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.
We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:
Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you.
Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.).
Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if you previously provided informed consent.
Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us.
Comply with a legal obligation.
Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.
Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights
To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either:
Calling us at 1-800-BALFOUR (800-225-3687)
Sending us an e-mail at privacy@balfour.com; or
Writing to us:
American Achievement Corporation
Attn: Privacy Officer 1550 W Mockingbird Lane Dallas, Texas 75235
Only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.
You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative.
Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.
Response Timing and Format
We endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. If you have an account with us, we will deliver our written response to that account. If you do not have an account with us, we will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option. Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable consumer request's receipt. The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.
We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.
Non-Discrimination
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:
Deny you goods or services.
Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Changes to Our Privacy Notice
We reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this privacy notice, we will notify you by email or through a notice on our website homepage.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or comments about this notice, our Privacy Statement, the ways in which we collect and use your personal information, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under California law, please do not hesitate to contact us through one of the following ways:
Calling us at 1-800-BALFOUR (800-225-3687)
Sending us an e-mail at privacy@balfour.com; or
Writing to us:
American Achievement Corporation
Attn: Privacy Officer 1550 W Mockingbird Lane Dallas, Texas 75235
Do Not Sell My Information
Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”),the sale of your personal information means the sharing of your personal information with certain third parties. Under the CCPA, consumers have the right to direct a business that sells personal information about the consumer to third parties not to sell the consumer’s personal information. Currently, we do not share your personal information in a manner that would be considered a sale under CCPA. We only disclose your personal information to our service providers pursuant to contracts that prohibit the service provider from using your personal information for any purpose other than those services specified in the contract.
Quick Links
Bulk Order Form
Download Order Forms
Shipping & Returns
Cap & Gown Colors
Cap & Gown History And Guidelines
Terms & Conditions
Measuring Guildelines
THE BASIC (GOOD)
THE CHANCERY (BETTER)
THE JURIST (BEST)
THE DIVINITY (BEST)
THE HERALD (GOOD)
THE WESLEY (BETTER)
M2000™LITTLE SCHOLAR™FREEDOM™FINEST QUALITY™ULTRA GREENWillsie Cap & Gown Co.®Graduate Choice™LUXURY CHAINETTE™
View all brands
All prices are in USD. © 2020 Willsie Cap & Gown. Sitemap
